[Music]
Hello Hello Friends Health Insurance Good
morning Amit Bhandari Welcome to the
best video
Today's topic is episode number two
questions and answers oh
so let's start today we will
try to take some more general council questions
go to the description of this video you will find two links I also have
a news channel behind me I interviewed him
plus then an article of his also came on
his website so during that interview
he asked a lot of questions so you
can see the answers of some general basic questions which are appointed by a lot of players by going to that video also let's
start the first question is my
group insurance policy this cancer day I got a
message from someone his policy was
running in some wax lead bank and
he had informed that bank in Hindi
that you cancel my flight close it
and after this
shift it to some other policy below
so look they have it all around the trailer
record speed what was the problem
that you clicked less  They will cancel the policy, they
broke the cancer, I had
sent them a notice, but for your second, like, please
import me, I
may reply to you, so until
your request for portability, which the
bank could have shifted from one company to another, is
not completed, you
basically have to tell them to cancel, so
generally, these bank policies have
a clear table in them,
very cheap products are launched,
people buy them after tracking, the problem is that
it is not sustainable, number two, there is
this phone etc. feeling in it, that
even after DTO third killing, the claim comes back, so you
always have to face this problem,
so try if
someone offers you such a policy,
I will not say here that such things are
not available, they are available, but
generally film studios have
very less such policies, because
people talk about policies in the wrong way or they are
not told, the other person does
not have the knowledge, so maybe one season  I am going to get a
medical checkup on Brightness.
We have discussed someone's study in it. If it takes
time, then look at that as well and will
put its description in the description within a few days.
So try to get a group insurance policy.
If it happens, you need to take very careful
steps. There will be a
dispute regarding the claim. The second question is that while
taking my health insurance policy, the
company did not do a free insurance medical
checkup. And just 15 years ago, if I had
taken any policy without a medical checkup, I would
not have got the policy. At
that time, in order to attract business, some companies did this by saying that they would
not do a health checkup on us till the age of four. So, okay, there was a
system, but if a medical checkup is done, then it is
believed and we also
feel that after that,
health issues start.
Because of this, if a free medical checkup is done, it is
good for us for the company.
What will happen? The company will impose a loading
more. This company has refused to give the hanging,
but it is better than taking a wrong
policy.  No, and what happened now is that 5 years
ago, there is a very great insurance company of India called
Gami, so they
started giving insurance up to the age of 60, 70, 80 without
medical checkup. Now what happened is that the
people in the middle will get some benefit,
so here the policy, its
business is based on underwriting,
underwriting wants the company to decide whether to
give insurance or
not, otherwise it is called medical and writing, so
when you have a
most important part of your reputation, that is,
like you
go to Amazon or Flipkart and find a product, then after that you say,
I want this, in such an insurance
company, there is a winter, they will stitch it, they will
not give it to you, they will charge more from you
or they will refuse, now they will put it
on meeting, so in the last few
years, when companies stopped doing physical health checkup,
then after that company,
gradually other companies started incurring losses, the
business of that company increased, so here
other companies started using editing,
now what happened was that
during the Corbett, this is called
hitting the lottery, without setting up near a medical center, the companies  If
someone has a dispute, the customer
's name is not written, so who will die of pain, then this is the
problem, the network of companies, the
attitude is that to hell with
underwriting, this is business, we
can go to any extent, some people's claims will get
rejected, so now a person is
sitting in Delhi, a person is sitting in Textiles,
a person is sitting in Golaghat,
his claim got rejected there, what difference does it make to him, so
this has unfortunately become a practice,
but there are 12 such companies in India,
your age is 18 years, even 25 years, you
will get a policy without a medical checkup,
then they will not give you the policy, you are a property buyer, so
I will give a very good like to this, yes, it is
not a religious rural famous company, so it did
not even spend money on ads, if we do the
policy properly, then I
love this company, but if you do not get a free insurance medical
checkup, then talk to your doctor,
he will determine your
condition, he has got every checkup done, after getting such a checkup done, you
can ask your company that
my medical checkup has been done.  Accept it, if the
tissue paper does not
break the record then that local will not get it done from you, for
any job SSC certified
standard will be followed in the entire legal system as
well, that is how you
can study yourself, so if you
want that where one company is
saying a little expensive policy but will
cut it like this, the other company is saying it is a little
cheaper but will not cut it like this, then
thank you, you are playing politics, who is
setting free insurance medical checkup,
saying that you will get a health checkup done, general
principles of getting a health checkup done after the age of 50, get it done by the
company without taking it,
understand that something is bound to happen, the
third question is tell me, my
policy was cancelled by the company citing Parikshit Singh disease, what
happened now, this is a
curse, earlier also I had talked in a video in the city,
some gentleman had
talked to the bank about the policy and why did the bank have it
because both the husband and wife are government
employees, so he went inside the bank and
talked to the relationship manager, brother we
also want a policy, now he is a little hilly  If they
lived in the area, they thought that it
is a bit difficult to navigate the government system, if they get a serious illness, they might have to go
to a big city, so by going there
we will get a good facility,
cashless facility will be available, there will be a limit on room rent,
both husband and wife are government employees,
this is a person who sleeps, buy a
Pulsar bike of Rs 15 lakh, now what is there, they get
some messages from private banks which
provide door step service, they know
all the things of your house, especially if it is feedback, if you
come home, if you have a cheque book, you can have
any doubt, for that also the company
provides such service for special entry customers, they have trust, so they
went and bought a Pulsar bike and within a few years
their claim came, when they got admitted in the hospital, the
company
cancelled it because the criteria of that policy was
that a person who has
diabetes is not given a policy, today
democracy, this was also with white, so
technically if they had deleted these things, it would have been
right for the company to give the policy, they would have given some
other product, now what happened to the question  The
relationship manager had done this policy for him,
he was very careful, he had an MBA
passport and was educated, he had an engineering
background but he was
educated only with the knowledge of finance, he did
not have practical knowledge and the company or the
bank had not even trained him and
his basic insurance work was not at all, he got him to
sign the policy sitting with the criminal,
after 4 years the company
rejected the claim due to this, he had made a comment, this is
why it was rejected, you yourself committed
fraud by telling him that you have diabetes, you did
not tell him at all, today you are telling the doctor and you did
not tell him while taking the policy, then what happened, the
company got defamed, that boy also got defamed,
his job has to be told, if this is heard on top of that then
a person's heart would have been broken, there was a loss of money, so it should have been there in this, after
reading the proposal form of the policy and signing it, the husband and
wife, if you are well educated then read the company's terms
and conditions, hey, if you are buying any account,
50,000 will be useful, 10,000,
₹5000 will be for only 500  If there is a cloth of Rs. 300 inside then we will
check that too, is it okay or
not, here you are living a Pulsar bike worth lakhs of rupees
and we don't even study, then that
for digit only God knows what should I say,
okay, some council
asked a question the day before yesterday whether we invest very little in mutual funds,
if I invest ₹100 somewhere, then I
put ₹5-10 in mutual funds, I have my own
training, my belief is a little work, I have a
personal Alice and it can also happen that
like I have an engineering background, this is a
little business of my Gurjar industry, if I have
interest then it is possible that I may invest somewhere else
or I like Reddy very much, so
many people say
that we have invested a lot in the indictment, we
mutual fund will give us 10-15 percent, I
feel that people do
not have the patience to invest so long in the market
that most of the people come out
tearing the second lead, the corporate governance issues in our India even in big mix, so my  I don't feel like it, it's my
personal thing, whatever you do, I
hire my financial experts. Thirdly,
I have thought that when we
talk about health insurance, then it's
okay and we forget it after taking the pass. If we invest in mutual
fund industry or striker, we
check it twice a day. If we were doing the market, then
I believe that within a year,
people waste a lot of their time. Chairman Rajinder
also says this. I do
n't want to do this. Aamir sometimes finds 67 percent
very good. The rate of
your white marketing is related to this. So, this
person's question came that we had a policy for
four years and today we had another
head injury and the company
rejected the claim. But what happened was that this
gentleman's son was driving the car and
he met with an
accident while driving. And we got a claim of Rs 67 lakhs. So
why was the claim rejected?
Because
he had green fever at that time.
Now, see, anything can happen and he may die.
Anything can happen because of green fever. But when you  Accident
claim prevails in Azhar case but
if the person is a criminal or belongs to
Congress which
happens due to alcohol drinking then the claim is
rejected because of that the company said that this was
not a rest, this relationship so generally Akhilesh got married
and there has been a loss also but
technical university is of
pornographic clip level but if he is an
unlawful criminal or if he himself is involved in
criminal activity then he gets
paid so unfriend him like the
claim got rejected a very strange
question has come that my commission to the insurance agent,
look here, it is
unlawful to ask for commission from anyone under the Insurance Act,
you can also be punished for this, secondly
if any person gives interest on his own,
that is also unlawful, now it happens like this,
many things are unlawful in India,
still corruption etc. keeps happening,
consider this thing as one thing that when you are
talking about a policy, you have to
take thousands of people under it and out of those
thousands, perhaps some of them may
also have taken birth from these thieves  He is getting commission to run the house
but
yours is fine, the money that is required for extracting is
very high, you have to
take thousands or lakhs of tourists every year, so when you are
taking export advice, you have a good
professional advisor, counselor,
agent, consultant, anything, a good
player, anyone, if he is good, is
involved in such practice, after getting good advice, people have
this question after 10th,
which line should we put our child in, and I
hear a lot of people like this, that
Ali became an advocate, became a doctor, and today she is
working in some other field, then so many years of
money and time is also wasted,
so much of youth time which could have been spent in studies
or could have left studies and done something else, in that
too she takes a better turn, so
guidance plays such a big role,
knowledge is not found without a guru,
God is not found without a guru, so when you want to live a
good life everyday, never talk about commission etc., then you must be
asking for a mission, that is why
I will not pick up your call,
if someone  Stay away from such questions that the person himself is discounted
because somewhere or the other
he will earn money but will also cause
loss to you. Thirdly, it can also happen that
if you send
a text to someone while buying a policy, he believes that it is unlawful,
but if I am repeating, he believes that it is liquid, then the
person in front of you can
tell you that the question is wrong and will not even fulfill his duty in telling you about your product which is being
backed in the proposal form or under
tension,
if it will not be of any use then
why will he appoint time for you. There are
many good games, so they do a
very good work in India,
they have set up their own people,
for film settlement, we have a
lot of people for position, so
our team is for claim settlement, we are going to
automate it all a little so that in the coming time,
your team can automatically provide service to our team through many good systems, so
now creating that time setup,
therefore it costs, tell me, if you have to do
something, go to the link on Twitter  I should have
left it at other places, as much as I do
n't earn as much as an advisor on one side, most of the government charges
18 percent, they get the
policy with so much difficulty, the government wo
n't say anything, GST of 98% is 25 percent, hey
friend, it shouldn't be more than 10:00 percent, so what are you
talking about, there is their channel there,
so let's be a little aware, it's not like
we spend our lives on whatever people around us complain about,
look a little out of the box, toe
boxing is a line we can use a lot, right,
eat and drink,
song, this is not life, earn some money,
build a car, this is not life,
how do you live your life, how do
you reach your position in the industry,
that you can leave these,
like there is a
line, there is a very good
black manual with a title, you had come, you got
discounts etc. Please never
ask for a service from someone who is running his house,
he owes you
petrol etc. under the policy, if you think this will happen then
please never practice this laughingly,
right  So the final question is
what things do we have to delete from this printed form and
what things do we not have to delete, show the setting of
free existing disease which is
a definition in the terms and conditions, it is
said that in the last 48 years
I have taken my policy and it should be mentioned in the
official, if you have any kind of
disease, then that condition, symptoms,
glasses, then it will be defined in your terms and conditions,
this is a section, it does
not work with people, from the time you were born till
today, have you ever undergone any treatment, have you got any
test done, have you ever fallen ill,
you have to delete some things from them,
all the things have to be removed, except for anything
except cold and cough, add everything in it only,
tell the things which have to be declared, this is
your
role to tell, whether printing is done in your policy or not, this is
not your job, it is the job
of the company, it has to be put in its flirting,
it has to be married, prince setting
definition, how does the company characterize, okay,
when I take the exam, I have to be a bank, that is  The
point has to be that if there is any special
point, most of the people forget to declare it
because nine out of 10
companies will not give your policy in case of this point
these days, so for you, you should understand that
selecting this policy is a very easy task,
when you have to back the policy properly,
your clean is hidden inside it, then do
not worry about pre-existing, do not
think too much, if any disease occurs after taking the policy, then
tell that to the company,
before taking the policy,
sit with your professional advisor and understand what all
this thing has happened in my life, till
now, my family, if you
take a policy for my child's parents, then I
talk to the bank people, they will type the land, in this there has
never been any disease, there is
only and only 10 years portion and never faced any
problem even once in my life,
then I will tell the doctor, then tomorrow you will be
tight with claim rejection, so try honestly,
if there is loading in your policy,
accept the
property of clean reaction, really really oppose
If you get loading done, some
person tells you that we will do the loading for you,
okay, if there is any
scheme from the company, accept it, definitely save your money,
if someone says I will get it done, then
greed arises, but stay away from such places,
giving loading improves your case, the
company, this is a matter of thought, I have told you honestly in the question, so
tomorrow who will go to Vimal court and it is
because of you that I told all this
and I paid extra money, okay, so
if you have no tension in getting paddy planted for Rs 1000-2000 per kg, then do it,
in the coming time you will get a claim of lakhs of rupees, that will be
settled from Ram, so all our
questions and answers end here, so in the
last some time,
we have stopped all our new disclosure videos, some of those
good videos are put in the description of this video,
deleted on our website, we keep adding something or the other in a few days, there is
information about the industry,
now you can go there and see our
These are ladies around 40-50 years of age,
for different types of demographics, so you
can gift by visiting our website. If
you like anyone, you
can add any of them online or WhatsApp our team,
you can also get the reply from there, there is a
contact form on the website, you
can also get the details. The basic purpose of this channel is that
we have made videos for any of you,
a common man who is not sitting in the city, but
sitting in the village, basically,
we
cannot reach there, you also
cannot reach us, many times we are nothing,
so by watching this edit video, you can understand
what things have to be taken care of in health insurance, whatever
work any person or palace complex,
our New Delhi Press Video Send is for you,
you should do the work CR, work honestly and well
and will serve the society, you are
buying a high policy, you cannot know our pet
practice, there is
nothing to worry about, watch these videos, you will
automatically get an idea of ​​many things,
you can easily buy the policy without paying any money.  If you
can, otherwise always take care of yourself,
always do something on the proposal form,
in a good video, if you liked something then you can
like this video, you can
subscribe to our channel,
if you liked it very much then go and share it a little bit
somewhere, on any channel, on Facebook, in
your WhatsApp group,
share it with your friends, even if you do it in a
simple way, then even after that these things will
reach them, come on, take
out your time to watch this video, thank you very much, thank you very much.